multiview.com 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy | MultiView

Effective Date: May 25, 2018

At Multiview, Inc. (together with our affiliates, “Multiview”, “we”, “us” and “our”), we take the privacy of your personal data seriously. This Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use, and share personal data you provide to us or relevant third parties in relation to our sites and services.

### What Personal Information Do We Collect?

We collect information about yourself or your company that you voluntarily provide us when you register to be a member of MultiView.com, register for certain services, or register for email newsletters and alerts. This information may include your name, email, phone, physical address, company name, and title. You may also provide additional comments on how you see the MultiView.com servicing your needs and interests. If you correspond with us by email, we will receive your email address and any information you include in your message. If you are a customer of our services, you may need to provide us certain payment information so that we can process your payments. Our customers may also provide us certain personal information that they have collected from their users.

### How Do We Use And Share Personal Information?

We use your personal information for the purposes for which you provided it, for other purposes you have consented to, or for purposes based on our legitimate business interests. These purposes may include to provide our services to you, administer your user account, respond to your inquiries or communications, resolve disputes, or register you for mailing lists you are interested in. If you wish to unsubscribe from any newsletters or marketing communications, please follow the unsubscribe or opt-out instructions in any such email, or notify us at any time by emailing us at [DataPrivacyOffice@multiview.com](mailto:DataPrivacyOffice@multiview.com).

We may enter into alliances, partnerships, or other business arrangements with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, telephone number, and email for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you. In connection with alliances, partnerships, or arrangements, we may also provide certain information to third parties if we have determined that the information will be used in a responsible manner by a responsible third party. We also share personal data with our third party services providers who use it to provide services on our behalf (such as our credit card payment processors). We may also transfer personal data in connection with a sale of the relevant business or another similar corporate transaction.

We may also use and share your personal information in limited circumstances where we deem reasonably necessary to comply with applicable law, respond to legal actions and orders, or protect our safety or rights or those of a third party.

If one of our customers provides us with personal information, we only use that information on such customer’s behalf, pursuant to its instructions.

### What Technical and Behavioral Information Do We Collect?

We use certain web technologies including cookies, web beacons, clear gifs, and pixels (collectively, “cookies and other technologies”) to provide our services. For more information about cookies and other technologies, please see the corresponding sections following this paragraph. These cookies and other technologies do not identify you personally, but provide technical and behavioral information such as the IP address, device type, browser type, and device identifier used to visit the website, the date and time of your visit, the pages you view, the websites you visited before and after visiting that site, which emails and advertisements you have been served and how you interacted with them, what kinds of web searches you have made, and (where permitted by your device) location data.

We use these cookies and other technologies on our own websites, and our customers also deploy our cookies and other technologies on their sites, news briefs, and product guides so that we can better provide our services to them.

**What Are Cookies?** — A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website that uses cookies, the corresponding web server asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. You can disable cookies by changing your browser settings, but this may disable certain functionality on websites that use cookies.

**What Are Web Beacons, Clear Gifs, and Pixels?** — These are three names for the same technology: a small or invisible image or other loadable element that can work independently or in connection with cookies to record certain technical or behavioral information regarding whether certain content has been delivered and accessed or viewed.

**Do Not Track** — Our services and sites currently do not recognize “do not track” signals that may be sent by certain browsers.

**Cross-Device Engagement** — If you use various devices to access relevant websites or services, our cookies and other technologies may use automated analysis to try and match your anonymous profile across your various devices. This enables us to better serve advertisements that may be of interest to you, and may also help us prevent you from seeing the same advertisements on various devices.

### How Do We Use And Share Technical and Behavioral Information?

We use technical and behavioral information gathered from the cookies and other technologies on our websites to differentiate you from other consumers so your “experience” is only available to you. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements, needing to log in more than is necessary for security, and remembering your saved preferences. Cookies, in conjunction with our web server’s log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our website and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our website and better serve our customers.

We use technical and behavioral information gathered from our cookies and other technologies on our customers’ websites to automatically build anonymous behavioral profiles. We may also use technical and behavioral information received from third party sources to help us build these profiles. These profiles do not identify you personally, but allow us to deliver advertisements that are more likely to be interesting or relevant to you (interest-based advertisements) on behalf of our customers. We may share technical and behavioral information and behavior profiles with our customers as part of working with them to determine what kinds of interest-based advertising to place, and where.

Disabling cookies on your device or browser may limit or prevent our building of behavioral profiles from your activities in the such device or browser. To fully opt-out of our building of behavioral profiles, please contact us at [DataPrivacyOffice@multiview.com](mailto:DataPrivacyOffice@multiview.com).

### Third Party Sites and Services

Our sites and services may include hyperlinks to third party sites and services (including those of our association customers, for example). If you visit or use such third party sites and services, please be mindful that the relevant third party (and not MultiView) controls the cookies and other technologies it uses on its sites and how it collects, uses, and shares personal information from you (although we remain responsible under this Policy if our customers implement our cookies and other technologies on their websites). We do not control such third parties and are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties. This Policy only governs our privacy practices; please review the applicable third party privacy policy when visiting or using any third party sites or services.

### EU and Swiss Residents

MultiView is based in the United States, and personal data collected by MultiView worldwide (including within the EU and Switzerland) may be transferred to the United States for processing. MultiView complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States. MultiView has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, MultiView commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of personal data from the EU and Switzerland. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our privacy practices should first contact us at [DataPrivacyOffice@multiview.com](mailto:DataPrivacyOffice@multiview.com). MultiView has further committed to cooperate with the panels established by the applicable EU or Swiss data protection authorities (DPAs) in the event that we cannot resolve your Privacy Shield complaint directly. If your complaint is still unresolved, then you may request binding arbitration pursuant to Annex 1 of the Privacy Shield, available at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction>.

In certain circumstances (such as when you voluntarily provide personal information to us through our website) we are the “data controller” as that term is used in applicable laws. In other circumstances, such as when we receive information from or on behalf of our customers, we are the “data processor.” If you have inquiries or requests in cases where we are the data processor, we may need to refer such inquiries or requests to the applicable data controller.

Under certain circumstances, we may remain liable for the acts of our third-party agents or service providers who perform services on our behalf for their handling of EU or Swiss personal data that we transfer to them.

### How Do We Protect Your Information?

We use commercially reasonable physical, technological, and administrative safeguards designed to protect your personal data from unauthorized use, access, or disclosure. Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private or sensitive information to us by email. Some of the information you may enter on our website may be transmitted securely via Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), 128 bit encryption services, which are enabled by a reputable SSL certificate provider (e.g., Thawte or Verisign). Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP.

### How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?

You may have the right to access the personal information that we hold about you and to request that we correct, amend, or delete it if it is inaccurate or processed in violation of applicable law. These access rights may not apply in some cases, including where providing access is unreasonably burdensome or expensive under the circumstances or where it would violate the rights of someone other than yourself. If you would like to request access to, correction, amendment, or deletion of your personal data, you can submit a written request to the contact information provided below. To protect your privacy, we will take commercially reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to or making any changes to your personal information. In some circumstances we may charge a reasonable fee for access to your information. If we deny your request, we will provide you with a written explanation of the reasons for our determination.

### Children

Our sites and services are not directed towards users under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect or process any personal data regarding such users. In the event that we discover we have collected personal data regarding such users, we will take commercially reasonable efforts to promptly remove such data from our systems.

### Consent and Contact

By using our website you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy practices, please contact us at [DataPrivacyOffice@multiview.com](mailto:DataPrivacyOffice@multiview.com).
